tentonhammer.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Ten Ton Hammer

### Keeping Your Personal Information Safe

Although we hope that our members get to know each other, you are not required to provide Personal Information to any member, and you should NEVER give your password to another member. Ten Ton Hammer encourages parents or guardians of minor members to be diligent and to supervise what their wards or children reveal to others. If you have problems with another member, or another member or visitor is not abiding by this Privacy Policy, please contact one of our administrators.

Ten Ton Hammer is committed to keeping your Personal Information safe. We have security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse or alteration of your Personal Information under our control. We use physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect our data, and only authorized personnel have access to most of your Personal Information. Credit and Debit card information is encrypted during transmission and is encrypted whenever it is not in use, and is not available to Ten Ton Hammer personnel.

Although we take precautions to prevent unfortunate occurrences, Ten Ton Hammer does not assume any responsibility or liability for acts of third parties or of employees or agents acting beyond their authority.

### Definition

" _Personal Information_ " means any information relating to your membership and use of the Site, and any information which identifies you or your account. This includes but is not limited to your name, address, email address, your password for Site access, and your telephone number.

### Disclosure

Please be aware that your user nickname and rating are visible to all members. Credit and debit card numbers are NOT visible to members and are also NOT visible to Ten Ton Hammer personnel. All other Personal Information is available to our administrators and to other authorized persons.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Master Games International, Inc. will not disclose your Personal Information to other members except as described in this Privacy Policy, unless we are compelled by law to do so. Should you disclose your Personal Information to another member, that member might disclose it to others with or without your permission. We do not assume any responsibility or liability should you voluntarily disclose your Personal Information to others.

You agree that we may sell, assign, license, or otherwise transfer to a third party your Personal Information in connection with a sale, assignment, joint venture or other transfer or disposition of a portion or all of the assets or shares of Master Games International, Inc. or its affiliates.

In our sole discretion, we still reserve the right to make exceptions whenever we believe that an emergency, illegal activity or other reasonable basis exists for notifying or providing your Personal Information to the appropriate authorities.

In order to combat spam and maintain the quality of the content on the Site, we may use textual analysis and other technologies when you submit comments or other information. For more information, [read the Mollom Privacy Policy](http://mollom.com/web-service-privacy-policy).

### Communication

Any communication with another member or visitor to the Site is NOT private and may be subject to review and disclosure by our administrators in the appropriate circumstances. Any communication with an administrator may or may not be private, depending on the situation.

### Right to Privacy

Your right to privacy is important to us. Ten Ton Hammer obtains certain Personal Information (as later defined) in order to provide our members with news, updates and other information we believe will be useful to you. Your Personal Information is provided to us upon registration and during your use of Master Games' internet sites. ("Site").

Ten Ton Hammer is committed to providing members with a Site that respects their privacy. Please review this Privacy Policy which is subject to change from time to time. Note, however, that this Privacy Policy only applies to our Site and does NOT apply to the web sites or Internet sites of any other person or entity. Should you have any questions or comments, please contact one of our administrators at **[admin-tth@tentonhammer.com](mailto:admin-tth@tentonhammer.com)**.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
